segpay.com 2015-02-20

# In order to provide you with interactive computer billing services, SegPay collects, uses, and shares certain information abou

Please read this privacy policy before using SegPay or submitting any personal information. By using SegPay, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy as well as SegPay’s Terms and Conditions. Please note that the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for SegPay only. If you link to other sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites. 

In order to provide you with interactive computer billing services, SegPay collects, uses, and shares certain information about you. The information SegPay collects helps us to better serve you and the online community by continually personalizing the electronic payment services we provide. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as processing your purchase request, responding to customer service inquiries, loss prevention, improving our service, communicating with you, and allowing our clients to provide customer service and fulfill their obligations to you.

**A. The Information SegPay Collects:**

1.       Information that we automatically receive: SegPay receives and stores certain information whenever you download web pages, or send us e-mail or forms. SegPay employs "cookie" and other tracking technology so that we can recognize you when you re-visit our URLs. Additionally, we automatically receive the IP address assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider. 

2.       Information that you provide to us: SegPay receives and stores all information that you enter on our website and our billing pages. This includes; a) for the credit card sign-up page: the url you are purchasing goods or services from or an e-ticket for, your e-mail address, your credit card number, your credit card expiration date, your user name and password, your first name, your last name, your address, your city, your state, your zip, your country, your IP address, and your agreement to be bound by SegPay's Terms and Conditions; b) for the check sign-up page: the url you are purchasing goods or services from or an e-ticket for, your bank's aba routing number, your checking account number, your check number, your e-mail address, y your user name and password, our first name, your last name, your date of birth, your phone number, your street address, your city, your state, your zip code, the name of the person on the account, your IP address, and your agreement to be bound by SegPay's Terms and Conditions. You are obligated to provide SegPay with accurate and up-to-date information, and failure to provide SegPay with such information could void any agreement between you and SegPay

3.       E-mail Correspondence: SegPay often requests a confirmation when you receive and open an e-mail communication delivered by SegPay. We archive all e-mail sent in and out of our network, and we identify the origination IP address of all e-mail sent into our network. We require that you refrain from forging headers or sending SPAM. 

4.       Information from third parties: From time to time, SegPay requests and receives information from third parties and compares it to the information that you have provided. The main purpose for this is that of loss prevention

**B. How Your Information May Be Shared:**

1.       SegPay may share your information law enforcement, government officials, or other third parties a) to comply with the law, b) if we are compelled to do so by a subpoena, court order or similar legal procedure to enforce our agreement, c) to protect the contract rights of our clients, d) if we believe in good faith that the disclosure of personal information is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss, e) to report suspected illegal activity, or f) to investigate violations of SegPay’s Terms and Conditions.

2.       SegPay passes the following data to its client, the owner/operator of the website from which you are purchasing goods and services utilizing SegPay a) for the credit card sign-up page: the url you are purchasing goods or services from or an e-ticket for, your e-mail address, your user name and password, your first name, your last name, your address, your city, your state, your zip, your country, and your agreement to be bound by SegPay's Terms and Conditions; b) for the check sign-up page: the url you are purchasing goods or services from or an e-ticket for, your e-mail address, your user name and password, your first name, your last name, your date of birth, your phone number, your street address, your city, your state, your zip code, the name of the person on the account, your agreement to be bound by SegPay's Terms and Conditions. 

3.       In addition, as part of the credit card processing system SegPay must provide certain information to the services that connect SegPay to the companies that perform the banking functions. The credit card associations have strict privacy rules that these companies must adhere to in order to be authorized to receive and process credit card transactions. 

**C. Protection of Privacy:**

1.       SegPay utilizes Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software when receiving and transmitting electronic payments. SegPay encrypts the information you provide. SegPay reveals on the last five digits of your credit card numbers when processing your transaction internally, and we reveal the entire number when communicating on a private dedicated line of communication with our acquiring bank. Additionally, SegPay employees the following security measures:

2.       SegPay conducts background and credit checks on all of its employees prior to employment. 

3.       SegPay employs a username password scheme in order to limit and archive access to its computer network by its employees, and third parties. Additionally, all information is stored behind firewalls and other security systems.

4.       SegPay's facility utilizes automatic locking doors that require a special security card for entry, and different levels of access exist throughout the SegPay campus

5.       SegPay will not store your payment or credit card number longer than twenty four (24) months. SegPay will not sell your information to any independent third party for any reason. SegPay will not disclose your credit card number or bank account number to anyone you have paid through SegPay except with your express permission or if we are required to do so to comply with a credit card rules, subpoena or other legal process.

6.       SegPay allows you to access to certain information about you for the limited purpose of viewing, updating, and in some instances deleting from our system any information deemed inaccurate. Any requests to access your information may be directed to: privacy@SegPay.com.

7.       SegPay does not request, or knowingly collect identifiable information from children under the age of 18. SegPay does not knowingly use or share personal information from users under the age of 18 with third parties. SegPay does not give children the ability to post messages or otherwise distribute information about themselves. SegPay does not offer children any promotions involving games, prizes, or any other activity that would induce a child to divulge personal information. 

8.       Opt-In: Other than detailed herein, SegPay will contact you and request your permission prior to sharing your data with third parties. SegPay will either contact you at the location provided by you at enrollment when we desire to share your information with a third party, or, SegPay will present you with a “check-box” requesting that you opt-in to any third party mailing lists.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy or regarding the information SegPay has stored about you, you should contact us by emailing us at privacy@SegPay.com or writing to us at SegPay, Inc., Attn: Privacy Department, 3111 N. University Drive, Suite 1000, Coral Springs, FL 33065

SegPay reserves the right to modify this policy at any time.
